# <UJJWOL THAPA>

Godawari, Lalitpur, Nepal +977-9840484872 ujjwolthapa0@gmail.com https://github.com/ujjwolth apa

Diligent individual having experience in networking and troubleshooting seeks a position in your firm with the aim to contribute to its organizational with the set of skills and having self motivation to learn new skills.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IT Intern

Dishhome pvt. Ltd. April 2022- July 2022

Completed three-month internship program. During the period I had the following roles and responsibility:

- Identify the causes of networking problems, using diagnostic testing software and equipment.
- Deploy and configure network devices such as Biometric Device, Router and Access Point with network software such as WDE, OSS and Care.
- Troubleshooting and solving the problem both in software and hardware.

### Web Developer Intern

A.M Nepal Pvt Ltd. Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

During Internship program I had following roles and responsibility:

- Content Migration of websites.
- Theme setup in Shopify
- Made Frontend in different shopify projects.

# **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATE**

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science** and **Information Technology**

Himalaya College of Engineering Kathmandu, Nepal [2017-2021]

## **DevOps Course**

Deerwalk Training Center Kathmandu,Nepal [2023]

# **Higher Secondary School**

Pinnacle Academy Lalitpur, Nepal [2015-2017]

# **SKILLS**

- Problem-solving, Teamwork, Adaptability
- Html,CSS,Python.
- Containerization: Docker, Kubernetes
- CI/CD: GithubActions
- Version Control: Git
- Cloud Infrastructure: AWS EC2, ECR

# **DEMO PROJECTS**

- ECOMMERCE REST API
- NODE CI
- CICD in AWS EC2
- ANSIBLE PLAYBOOK
- KUBERNETES PRACTICE